Guide to the Barbara Booker collection, 1935-2002.
Booker, Barbara collection.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Barbara Booker collection, 1935-2002.
4752
Booker, Barbara.
1.3 cubic feet.
Correspondence, Memorabilia, Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes records pertaining to various track and cross-country skiing races and events, including meet results, workout schedules and memorabilia.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Barbara Booker was an avid runner, camper, hiker, triathlete and cross country skier and the first woman president of the Finger Lakes Runners Club. Under her direction the club began to focus on open competition and women's running in road races and marathons.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes records pertaining to various track and cross-country skiing races and events, including meet results, workout schedules and memorabilia.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Booker, Barbara; Cornell Masters Mile.; Finger Lakes Runners Club.
Subjects:
Running.; Running--Training.; Marathon running.; Cross-country skiing.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Barb Booker, 1935-2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Executive Committee Meetings, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- FLRC Documents, 1977-1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- FLRC History, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Photos, 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Monthly Meet Results, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Monthly Meet Results, 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Course Maps, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 Communications, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Misc. Info. On local Runners, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Ithaca 5 & 10, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 Volunteers/Committees, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 receipts and Accounts, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Skunk Cabbage Race, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 Results, 1980-1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Fun Runs, Etc., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- FLRC Annual Banquet, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Meet Sanctions, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Masters Mile (Womens), 1981-1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Masters Mile, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Masters Mile, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Masters Mile, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Masters Mile For Women, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Masters Mile, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- YMCA Run, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Misc. Race Results, 1973-1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- National Run Data Cnt., 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Club Event Announcements, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Old Rosters, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Road Runners Club Info., 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Tortoise & the Hare 10k, 1993-2002 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Empire Haven Clover Runs, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Tom B. Trail Runs, 1990-2002 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Newspaper Articles, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Monster Marathon & ½ Marathon, 1990-2002 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Finger Lakes Fifties, 1989-2002 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Forest Frolic 7k & 15k, 1989-2002 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Forge the Gorges, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Danby Down and Dirty, 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Virgil Mountain Madness, 1986-2002 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Cornell Golf Course Cross Country Meet, 1989-1993 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Ed’s Ultra 27 mile trail run, 1989-1995 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Virgil mountain Scramble, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Freihofer’s Run for Women, 1978-1986 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Finger Lakes Marathon, 1977-1975 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Boston Qualifier, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- The Athletic Conference (TAC), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- General Information on Running, Various (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Glimmerglass Triathlon, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- X-Country Ski Information, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Lawrence Loppet (Lake Placid) Results, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Tug Hill X-Country Ski, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Chantanqua Ski Marathon, 1979-1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Canadian Ski Marathon, 1971-1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Cayuga Nordic Ski Club, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Cross Country Ski Maps, Various (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Clare DeBoer’s Cayuga Lake Swim, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)